掌声鼓励黛拉·凯尔
Let's hear it for Della Carr.
老兄  你姐姐真帅呆了
Dude, your sister kicks serious ass.
今年她还参加了男孩组的比赛
Competed in the boy's league this year.
把他们打得落花流水
Kicked their asses, too.
干得好  小黛  你
Nice job, Del. You--
用50毫米乘50毫米的鞋  我滑得更快
I went faster on the 50-50.
你说对了
You were right.
下一个谁来试试
All right, who wants next?
好吧  我有点偏心眼
Yeah, yeah, I'm a little biased.
定做滑板
Custom decks.
400美元起价
Start the bidding at 400 bucks.
相信我  孩子们会想法设法让家长们来买
Trust me, the kids'll force their parents to buy them.
快来看看
You got to see this.
你今天办了一件大事
You made a great event today.
够快了吗
Fast enough for you?
我都已经残疾了
I'm already in a wheelchair.
你还怕什么呢
What are you so afraid of?
我可没想这么玩
That wasn't what I meant.
黛拉  你还好吗
Della? You okay?
爸爸妈妈快来啊
Mom! Dad!
我们别再这样停车了
We got to stop parking like this.
别人会说三道四的
People are gonna talk.
所以我想先和你谈谈
Well, that's why I plan on doing some talking first.
我想正式告知人力资源部我们在交往
I want us to formerly report our relationship to Human Resources.
没问题  你告诉他们  我负责通知其他人
Okay. You get them, I'll cover everybody else.
如果能等在那个会后
I would appreciate it
再公开我们的关系  我会非常开心
if we could keep it quiet until we had that meeting.
不能一直抓着你的屁股  这一天会很难熬
It's gonna be hard with me grabbing your ass all day.
一开始就不许抓
Grabbing stops at the threshold.
进到停车场开始算起
Of the parking garage.
我是瘸子
Handicapped plates.
我有特殊权限
I got special access.
我只是不希望我们的感情影响到工作
I just don't want our relationship affecting our jobs.
反之亦然
Or the other way around.
卡迪医生  周末过得如何
Why, Dr. Cuddy, how was your weekend?
我接到一通电话  你有病人了
I got a call about a case for you.
一个14岁的孩子
14-year-old.
内科急救专家认为她的心脏不跳了
EMTs think her heart stopped--
听起来不错
Sounds great.
你还没看呢
You haven't seen it yet.
我感到它在吸引着我
I sense something fascinating about it.
今天下午我们去见人力资源部的人
I'm gonna get us in to see HR this afternoon.
在那之前你能保持沉默吗
Think you can hold your tongue till then?
是  妈妈
Mom...
那好  大家很快就会知道的
Fine. People are gonna know soon enough.
午饭之前我会保密
I think I can hold it till lunch.
我和卡迪在约会
I'm seeing Cuddy.
概括来说  已经裸裎相见了
Generally, without her clothes on.
发挥下想象力
Use your imagination.
最好想象力丰富点
Hope it's got a wide-angle lens.
其实你并不需要这个
You don't actually need that.
我得回办公室看看有没有放屁坐垫
I'm gonna go check my office for whoopee cushions.
这不是恶作剧
This is not a prank.
走出这房间的人不是我
This is not me walking out the door.
真的吗  你和卡迪
Really? You and Cuddy?
千真万确  福曼能解释给你们
For reals. Foreman can translate.
看看这位全能初中生小姐
So Junior Miss Everything--
滑板选手  篮球运动员
Skateboarder, basketballer,
科学俱乐部会员  集邮俱乐部会员
science clubber, seal clubber.
最后一个其实是我猜的
I'm actually guessing with that last one.
之前很健康  忽然就心律失常
Healthy one day, heart arrhythmia the next.
你确定和高层扯上关系
Are you sure it's a good idea
是好主意吗
to be yanking on the chain of command?
就该这么做  豪斯
Way to go, House.
我很惊讶你们竟然才开始交往
I'm surprised you two didn't get together sooner.
心电图  超声波和头部扫描都没有发现问题
EKG, echo and head CT are all spotless.
神经检查也没有发现异常
There's nothing on her neurological exam.
有兴趣  赞成的  愤慨的  中立的
Interesting. In favor, indignant, indifferent.
我还需要一个女性的观点
Think I'd like a female perspective.
-或者是十三的  她在哪  -她走了
- Or Thirteen's. Where is she? - She's gone.
她说要离开一段时间
She said she was taking a leave of absence.
想让我们以为
Wanted us to think
她是去罗马的亨廷顿症研究中心
it was for a Huntington's study in Rome.
但那边没听说她要参加
They've never heard of her.
手机和家里电话都联系不上她
Cell and home phone are disconnected.
公寓里的东西也搬走了
Apartment's already been vacated.
你的死神头骨手杖哪里去了
And what's with the death's head cane?
没有我这型号的死神屁股手杖出售
They didn't have a death's ass cane in my size.
我们只能等了
Well, I guess we'll just have to wait.
等引起间歇性心律不齐的条件出现  陶博
Conditions that cause intermittent heart arrhythmias. Taub.
三年来  你一直想把十三挤走
Three years, you've been trying to game out Thirteen,
现在你又不在乎了
And now you don't care?
抱歉  不关心十三
Sorry. Not caring about Thirteen
不是诊断心律不齐的一部分
is not part of the differential for heart arrhythmia,
但是你可以拿到这个游戏的家庭版
but you do get a home version of the game.
病人的弟弟患有严重的先天性肌营养不良症
Patient's brother has severe, congenital muscular dystrophy.
这种病的平均寿命为25岁
Life expectancy of about 25.
如果她有潜在症状...
If she's had a latent case of it...
这病不会突然发作  福曼
Wouldn't be sudden onset. Foreman.
关于十三  你知道什么我们不知道的吗
Do you know something about Thirteen that we don't?
她有权保留隐私
She's entitled to her privacy.
就像我有义务诊断病因
Just as I'm entitled to a diagnosis.
你现在试图隐瞒十三离开的原因
And you're glossing over Thirteen's departure
是因为你真的尊重他人隐私吗
because you actually respect somebody's privacy?
我同意你的说法  我不关心这事才奇怪
I agree. It's weird of me not to care.
所以要么我因为卡迪变了个人
So either I'm a changed man because of Cuddy,
要么我假装变了个人
or I'm pretending to be a changed man
因为我确实知道十三的事
because I do know something about Thirteen
还不愿告诉你们
and I'm trying to throw you off the scent,
要么就是因为我失去一个病人成了疯子
or I've just gone nutty bananas because I lost a patient.
我诊出病因之后
All of which you are free to discuss
随便你们猜测
after I get a diagnosis.
如果是长Q-T间期综合症的话
If it's Long QT Syndrome,
那么在滑板场地的任何惊吓刺激
any startling stimulus in that skate park
都能够引发心律不齐
could have triggered the arrhythmia.
噪音太大  灯光太耀眼
Loud noise, flashing lights.
把病人吓死就能证明是长Q-T间期综合症
Scare the patient to death to confirm Long QT.
好吧  如果你们坚持要做
Fine. If you insist,
就找个能把病人救回来的地方
do it in a room with one of those thingamabobs that brings people back to life.
惊吓测试太疯狂了
Scare test is insane.
惊吓测试很合理
Scare test is legitimate.
能够模拟真实世界的情况
Simulates real world conditions.
和卡迪的交往这事太疯狂了
This fling with Cuddy is insane.
信号枪  够吓人了吗
Flare gun? Scary enough?
怎么告诉她我们要做这个愚蠢的测试呢
How about just telling her we're planning this stupid test?
希望豪斯和卡迪不只是一时冲动
And I'm hoping House and Cuddy are more than just a fling.
很显然豪斯陷进去了
It's clearly mellowed him out.
他甚至都不关心十三了
He didn't even care about Thirteen.
对  让我们吓死病人的人
Right. The guy who ordered us
已经陷进去了
to stop the patient's heart has mellowed out.
如果是命中注定就太可怕了
It's gonna be horrible because it's doomed,
这会让豪斯更加诡异
which is just gonna make House 50 times more of a crank.
可以用爆竹
Firecrackers.
我们可以藏在食物托盘下面
We can hide 'em under one of those covered food trays.
在手帕里发现搔痒粉了吗
Find any itching powder in your hanky?
在抽屉里发现假便便了吗
Any fake poo in your desk drawer?
没有  没发现恶作剧道具这个证据
Yes, the lack of dime-store pranks
确实能证明你和卡迪在交往
is proof that you're actually dating Cuddy,
也证明了你不是在嘲弄我的担心之情
And not just mocking me for being worried about you.
为什么我非要证明给你看呢
What do I have to do to prove this to you?
把我的手杖纹在她大腿内侧
Tattoo a cane on her inner thigh?
把她大腿内侧纹在我手杖上
Tattoo her inner thigh on my cane?
你诏告天下了  是吗
You told everybody, didn't you?
再说一次  这个人不相信
Repeatedly. This one's not buying it.
-需要你帮个小忙  -我不想强迫别人相信
- Need a little help. - I'm not selling it.
我们该去人力资源部了
It's time for our meeting at Human Resources.
人力资源部
Human Resources.
现在我为什么要去人力资源部
Now, why would I need to go to Human Resources?
豪斯  之前六周
House, you've been to Human Resources
你去了人力资源部74次
74 times in the last six weeks.
你不相信  我就不去
Never after doing this.
-我相信了  -拜托  浅吻而已
- Well, I'm convinced. - Come on. One peck.
刺激他一下就行
Just enough to arouse him a little.
我...我甚至...
I--hey, I'm not even...
我没说你
I didn't mean you.
-如果我证实了  我们能走了吗  -能
- If I confirm it, can we leave? - Yes.
我们在交往
It's true.
我对我叔祖母都比这热情
I've been more passionate with my great aunt.
梅布尔吗  向她致敬
Mabel? Up high.
这样可以了吗
We done here?
她甚至没让我咳一声
She didn't even ask me to cough.
貌似你稍微矫正了我的瘸腿
Think you straightened out my limp a little.
怎样描述你们关系的确切性质
How would you describe the exact nature of the relationship?
你看过动物王国吗
You ever see Wild Kingdom?
那些昆虫在交配之后  会扯掉配偶的头
Those insects that rip their partner's heads off after copulating?
是性关系
It's a sexual relationship.
慢点说  他要记下来
Go slowly now. He's writing it down.
我相信我仍然能够
I believe that I can still
有效监督豪斯医生
supervise Dr. House effectively,
但是我们都会严格遵守医院规章制度
but we both want to follow hospital policy to the letter.
我们关心的是确保
Our concern is to make sure
不发生利益冲突
that there's no conflict of interest,
不对医院产生不利影响
no liability for the hospital.
如果事情变糟  你觉得我们会起诉吗
You think we're gonna sue if things go south?
-老实告诉你吧  事实上她会...  -豪斯
- Let me tell you. She actually does go... - House.
不要插嘴
Let him talk.
我知道你们不会起诉
I, uh, know that you're not going to sue,
因为你们要签一份爱情合约
because you are both going to sign love contracts.
双方确立关系协议
Consensual relationship agreements.
显然外部委员会
Well, obviously outside council
将要复查内衣条款
will have to review the crotchless undies clause.
我们也会注意对于豪斯医生的偏袒行为
Uh, we'll also need to watch for any favoritism toward Dr. House.
这意味着她要和大家发生关系吗
Does that mean she has to sleep with everyone?
我发誓不会给他加薪或者升职
I promise not to give him a raise or a promotion of any kind.
有一个关于
There's got to be a joke there
适应通货膨胀的笑话
about keeping up with inflation.
或者对他的偏见
Or bias against him.
豪斯医生最近的病例
Are there any supervisory issues
有监管问题吗
with Dr. House's current case load?
没有  她的病解决了
No, her case is solved.
病人患有长Q-T间期综合症
Patient has Long QT.
我们打算把她吓死来确认病情
Gonna scare her into cardiac arrest to confirm it.
-不会  我们没这打算  -好吧  没这打算
- No, we're not. - Okay, no, we're not.
怎么样  一切在你掌握之中
See? Everything's under control.
我知道你还想做那个愚蠢的惊吓测试
I know you're still planning your ridiculous scare test.
病人的情况还不足以冒这个险
The patient is nowhere near sick enough to justify the risk.
血管造影片和心电图
An angiogram and an E.P. study
更安全有效
are much safer and very effective.
观点不错  不做惊吓测试了
Fair point. Not doing the scare test.
我邀请你来监督我不做这个测试
I'd invite you to watch me not doing the test,
但是之前很多次没有做
but having not done it many times before,
相信我  真的很无聊
trust me, it's pretty not interesting.
-豪斯  -惊吓测试的请求没有通过
- House? - Scare test was not approved.
先用血管造影法和心电图
Do an angio and E.P. Study instead.
首先  这两种办法效率比较低...
First of all, that's not as effective as--
为什么不做更专业点的测试
How come you're not doing the more specialized test?
实际上  这个测试比较有效
This test is virtually just as effective.
而且  豪斯医生把病人的安全放在首位
And Dr. House puts a premium on patient safety.
但他经常改变主意
But frequently changes his mind.
雨果  放过他吧  我没事
Hugo, give him a break. I'm fine.
我们开始之前你应该去趟厕所
You should go to the bathroom before we go.
给你补液有些时候了
We've been hydrating you for quite a while.
我不想上厕所
I don't have to pee.
一旦我们开始测试
Once we start the test,
至少一小时后你才可以走动
you won't be able to move for at least an hour.
我真的不想上厕所
I really don't have to pee.
我们给她补了多少液体
How much fluid have we given her?
2.5升  你上次上厕所是什么时候
2.5 liters. When's the last time you went to the bathroom?
大概是昨天晚上吧
Last night, I guess.
那说明什么
What does that mean?
看来你们女儿的肾功能衰竭了
Your daughter's kidneys seem to be failing.
是什么引起她心脏停止跳动
So what could cause her heart to stop
又不排尿呢
and her urine not to drop?
豪斯  我以为长远来看
House, I was expecting your relationship with Cuddy
你和卡迪的关系会使我们工作更复杂
to complicate our work long-term.
但我现在担心这样的关系在目前就会发挥作用
I am now concerned it might be affecting us short-term.
-恕我直言  -恕不接受
- All due respect. - None taken.
我一直都很听卡迪的话
I listen to Cuddy all the time.
她是我上司  同样也是你们的上司
She's my boss. Also yours, by the way.
你听她的意见  然后告诉她说她是个白痴
You'd listen, then tell her she's being an idiot,
接着依然我行我素
and do whatever you want.
我想当她不是白痴的时候我可以跳过"白痴"的部分
I find I can skip the idiot part when she's not being an idiot,
既然惊吓测试
and since the scare test
也会造成同样的僵局
would have led to the same dead end,
她很明智地阻止了这一行为
she was right to stop it.
也就是说你的问题是你自己
Which means your problem's about you.
这论调有点意思
This should be interesting.
失败者需要爱的关怀
Losers love company.
就算是像我一样的厌恶人类者
And if even a misanthrope like me
也能有机会得到幸福
has a chance at happiness,
不然在"失败者王国"该有多寂寞啊
it's gonna be pretty lonely on that landfill of loserdom
也就是你说的婚姻
you call a marriage.
心脏停跳  肾衰竭  开始
Heart, kidneys, go.
可能是法布里病
Could be Fabry disease.
-油脂在她器官组织沉积  -她父亲没有类似病史
- Lipid deposition in her tissues. - Dad's history was clean.
如果是蛋白质沉积物呢
What about protein deposits?
这就不会出现在她父母的病史上
They wouldn't show in her parents' history.
淀粉样变性病  能同时解释这两个症状
Amyloidosis. Explains both the symptoms.
用骨髓移植来治疗
Marrow transplant to treat.
她弟弟可以
Brother's a match.
确诊后做手术
Confirm and do.
我最近常感觉很疲劳
I been experiencing fatigue,
还有浑身无力
and--and weakness.
这很正常
Wouldn't have anything to do with the fact
因为你已经  102岁了
that you're... 102 years old.
但他通常都强壮如牛
Usually he's strong as an ox.
102岁的牛
102-year-old ox.
他的脚和腿有麻刺感
He has tingling in his feet and his legs.
我想要帮他做一套完整的测试
I want a full battery of tests.
-碳元素年代测试吗  -如果医保不够我会付现金
- Carbon dating?  - I'll pay cash if it's not covered.
你还真会为你朋友考虑啊
That's nice of you to float your friend.
他不是我朋友  他是我父亲
He's not my friend. He's my father.
他比我老22岁
He's 22 years older than me.
没错  他的下颚也是这么告诉我的
Well, that's true, he's definitely had his jowls done.
就统计上说  如果他没有这些症状
Statistically, if he didn't have these symptoms,
他就会像绝大多数他这个年龄的人一样
he'd be like most people of his age--
死了好几十年了
dead for the past several decades.
给我做测试  我生病了
Do the tests. I'm sick.
你有这些症状是正常的
You have a bad case of natural causes.
尽管给他做测试就是了
Do the damn tests.
如果指管里盛满了沙子
If the vial fills with sand,
那真是个不好的症状
we take that as a bad sign.
雨果可以留在这里的  你们为什么让他离开
Hugo should be here. Why'd you ask him to leave?
我们希望能跟你深入的谈论这事
We wanted to be able to discuss this openly.
但这样做明显也涉及到了他
But it obviously affects him.
宝贝  听医生说完
Honey, let the doctor finish.
标准程序是这样的
It's a standard procedure.
我们给你进行全身麻醉
we use general anesthesia,
切取一小部分
harvest a very small amount of--
不  我是不会接受我弟弟的骨髓的
No. I'm not taking my brother's marrow.
-小黛  这  -这样的取样是完全无害的
- Del, it's--  - these harvests are harmless.
加上我们的用药
With the meds we give,
几乎完全无痛
there's almost no pain,
也基本没有感染的可能
almost no risk of infection.
几乎  他的人生已经够艰难的了
Almost? His life's hard enough as it is.
治疗遇到点小挫折
Small problem with the treatment.
病人不肯要轮椅弟弟的骨髓是吗
Patient won't take marrow from steel wheels?
你怎么知道  我们正在找其他匹配者
We're finding another match. And how do you know?
还能有什么问题
What other problem could there be
手术程序又没问题
with a problem-free procedure?
男性体育  科学学会
Boy's sports, science club,
她在为他过生活  不是自己
she's living his life, not hers.
这就说明她是个自我牺牲的呆瓜
Makes sense she's being a self-denying moron.
她爱自己的弟弟  她的想法很无私
She loves her brother. She's thinking selflessly.
-那怎么会是  -笨蛋吗
- How is that at all - Being moronic?
我只想到她刚才拒绝了一项
Mm. If I can only think of a harm-free medical treatment
无医学创伤的治疗
she turned down lately.
你说得对  如果人人都更自私一点
You're right. If everyone were more selfish,
世界将变成更美好的人间
the world would be a better place.
看见没  当你不是白痴的时候
See? I can skip the idiot part
我可以跳过"你是白痴"的部分
when you're not being an idiot.
你好  开始的48小时我和你现在的表情一样
Yeah, I had that same facial expression for the first 48 hours.
还有另一个表情  不过每次都只持续了15秒
Had another one too, but only for 15 seconds at a time.
我为你高兴  你也很为自己高兴
I'm happy for you. You're happy for you.
这是件大事
This is huge.
-那谁来监督你  -卡迪
- So who's gonna supervise you? - Cuddy.
我想那或许能管用吧
Well, I guess maybe that can work.
什么或许  不都还是老样子吗
Maybe? Nothing's changed.
你在门诊时间自觉现身
You showed up for clinic hours. Voluntarily.
行了  发生了小小的改变
Fine. A little bit has changed.
豪斯  一切都变了
House, everything's changed.
你们睡在一起
You're sleeping together.
除了对你病人的"惊吓测试"的首肯
You want something from her
你还希望能从她那里得到爱
besides a sign-off on scaring your patient to death.
你找过陶博
You talked to Taub.
他很担心你
He's worried about you.
-他是个混蛋  -我也很担心你
- He's a jerk.  - I'm worried too.
我有必要再重复一遍吗
Do I need to say it?
我希望你们能好好相处
I want this to work.
我又没改变我的做事风格
I'm not doing anything differently.
她只不过让我取消了一项诊断测试
She changed my mind about one diagnostic test.
何况她是对的
And she was right.
就算你天生就爱担心我
Even though it's your emotional default,
放心吧
stop worrying.
我能处理好
I can handle it.
我听说你是个铁杆滑板运动员
I hear you're a pretty fier skateboarder.
还行
I do okay.
你参加这些运动  难道人们不觉得
All your activities, don't they seem like things
这应该是16岁的男孩玩的吗
a 16-year-old boy would do?
有些人会认为
Some people might think
你在为他过生活
you're trying to live his life for him.
的确  多少有一些
I am. Sort of.
我开始玩滑板
Um, I got into skateboarding
是因为雨果的同学在玩
when some of Hugo's classmates did,
他知道他永远都不可能做到
and he realized he could never do it.
很多事情都是这样
It's the same with a lot of things.
我们总是一起面对
We live through it together.
你也不担心自己太过于无私
And you're not worried you're being selfless
以至于到自我牺牲
to the point of self-denial?
你从未受到过别人的鼓舞吗
You've never been inspired by someone?
快把药给吃了吧
Why don't you take your pills?
这里需要人手帮忙
Need some help in here.
胸腔积血  需要对她进行支气管镜检查
Hemothorax. We need to bronch her now.
准备一间手术室
Clear an O.R.
她被自己的血呛到了
She's drowning in her own blood.
这不是淀粉样变性病
It's not amyloidosis.
她快要流血身亡了  从肺里往外冒血
She's bleeding to death. Out of her lung.
我想用泡沫填充1/4的肺
I want to fill a quarter of it with foam.
那确实能止血
That'd stop the bleeding, all right.
我想这比控制饮食经常锻炼来的有用吧
Thought it made more sense than diet and exercise.
如果她剩下的肺不能正常工作
And if she doesn't have enough lung function left,
你这样做就会杀死她
you'll have killed her.
剩下唯一的选择就是缓慢缝合肺部
The only alternative is slowly suturing the lung,
我们就默默祈祷出血能及时止住
hoping that the bleeding stops in time
她不会把自己给弄死吧
and she doesn't die on her own.
但我们就能清白的大步走开
But we would walk away with clean hands.
除了手术时弄到身上的血
Except for all the blood.
你是对的  更快更险的招比较好
You're right. Faster and riskier's better.
给肺部填充泡沫
Foam the lung.
获得批准了吗
Got a green light?
没有  给肺部做缝合
No. Suture the lung.
手术刀  肋骨撑开器
Scalpel, rib spreader.
我处理不来
I can't handle it.
发生什么了
What happened?
她说了"同意"  但我听到了"不同意"
She said "Yes," And I heard "No."
当然我没有听到她说"不同意"
I didn't actually hear "No."
我就是  很确定她是这个意思
But I just...was sure that's what she meant.
她歪了下头  皱了下眉
Way she tilted her head and half-arched her eyebrow.
我为什么要在乎她的想法
What do I even care what she meant?
她同意了  这才是关键
She said yes. That's all that matters.
我会把这事稿砸的
I'm screwing this up.
这不算太糟糕  豪斯
It's not completely bad, House.
你很在意她所以没有胡作非为
You care enough to pull your punches.
这是好事
That's not a bad thing.
但你和卡迪得想个办法
But you and Cuddy have got to figure out a way
避免再出现这种问题
of avoiding this problem.
约法三章
Set some ground rules.
没错  我要避免这种问题发生
Yeah. I have to avoid this problem.
如果我们的相互作用
If I can restrict our interactions
只停留在我们穿内裤的地方
to places where neither of us are wearing pants...
这样才不能避免问题发生
Yeah, that's not avoiding the problem,
那是避免发生争执
that's avoiding the issue.
显然逃避是我处理发生争执的方法
Since avoidance is my plan for dealing with the issue,
理论上来说  我没有在避免发生争执
technically, that's not avoiding it.
-谢了  -客气
- Thanks.  - No problem.
-缝合还算有用  -这次
- Stitching worked. - This time.
下次请示卡迪可能还是行不通
No guarantee bowing to Cuddy will work next time.
心律失常  肾衰竭
Heart arrhythmia, kidney failure,
现在又有肺出血
and now bleeding lung.
我不想批评你的女朋友  但是
I don't want to criticize your girlfriend, but--
这几年你一直要我
Hey, you've been on me for years
尊重别人的意见
to respect someone's opinion.
别因为我要离开你们
Just 'cause I had to go outside this group
去找我尊重的人而吃醋
to find one I respect.
多系统脏器病变  肺部为主
Multi-system involvement centered in the lung.
-可能是结节病  -不能解释胸腔积血
- Sarcoidosis?  - Doesn't explain the hemothorax.
结核病能损伤三个器官
TB can affect all three organs.
皮肤反应测验结果呈阴性
Skin test was negative.
会不会是古德帕斯丘综合症
What about goodpasture's?
会损伤肺和肾
Affects the lungs, kidneys.
自身免疫能解释意外的心律失常
And autoimmune explains the out of the blue arrhythmia.
是古德帕斯丘综合症
Goodpasture's it is.
用免疫抑制剂和血浆除去法治疗
Immunosuppressants and plasmapheresis to treat,
进行肾活组织检查确认
kidney biopsy to confirm.
豪斯医生
Dr. House.
别告诉我说你父亲的发际线在后退
Don't tell me, your father's hairline is receding,
他需要更多测试
and he needs more tests.
他102岁了  下次检查就该是验尸了
He's 102. His next test is an autopsy.
听着  我爱老爹
Look, I love the old man,
但是我得把他从房子里弄走
but I got to get him out of the damn house.
没有我  他什么也干不了
He can't do anything without me.
他得去养老院
He needs to be in a care facility.
这样的话  直说无妨  他不是小孩了
Well, so tell him. He's a big boy now.
我不能  我是他生活的全部
I can't. I'm his whole life.
但是  要是这话出自医生之口
But if it comes from a doctor...
若你30岁的话  出手很大方啊
That's very generous. When you were 30.
假装做做检查  完了告诉他
Pretend to run the tests, and then tell him...
他不能继续和我一起住了
He can't live with me anymore.
整个下午我都没遇见你  我想你了
I didn't run into you all afternoon. I missed you.
忙啊
Busy day.
或许我们明天该一起吃午餐
Maybe we should plan on lunch tomorrow.
问题是  午餐时间  你是穿着衣服的
Problem is, at lunch you tend to wear tops.
这样好太多了
This is much better.
卡迪和我光着呢
Cuddy and I are naked.
所以我没法集中精神
So I'm having trouble focusing.
说简单点
Use small words.
肾脏活检结果没问题
Kidney biopsy was clean,
所以我们复检了手术室得到的肺部组织
So we rechecked the piece of her lung from the O.R.
我糊涂了
You lost me.
抱歉  谁打电话来着
Sorry, who is this calling again?
不是肺出血肾炎综合征
It's not goodpasture's.
血管内膜有增厚
There's intimal thickening of the blood vessels.
以及淋巴细胞渗透
And lymphocytic infiltrate.
我们针对淋巴管平滑肌瘤检测  是阳性
We tested for lam. It's positive.
此外  她的肺没用了
Plus her lung's fried.
要保命  她需要肺部移植
She needs a donor lung to live,
那也是治疗淋巴管平滑肌瘤的唯一方法
Which is the only treatment for lam, anyway.
陶博已经去移植委员会了
Taub's gone to the transplant committee.
他们可能已经找到供体肺了
They may have found a donor lung.
那么这个电话就是为了通知我一下咯
So this call is purely expositional.
我真的得穿衣服了
I should really get dressed.
我告诉过保姆  我9点会到家的
I told the nanny I'd be home by 9:00.
我塞了40块钱给保姆
And I slipped the nanny 40 bucks,
让她留到11点
Told her to stay till 10:00.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Mm-hmm, really.
好消息
Good news.
手术顺利
Surgery was uneventful,
但进入恢复期约一小时后供体肺开始衰竭
But the donor lung started failing about an hour into recovery.
我们知道是淋巴管平滑肌瘤病没错
We know we're right about lam.
检测结果已证实
Tests confirmed it.
那么就只有两个可能
That leaves us with two options.
身体排斥新肺
Body's rejecting the new lung
或者我们该拒用新肺的
Or we should have rejected the new lung
因为它已被感染
Because it's infected.
做活检  看看是哪个
Let's biopsy, see which one it is.
没法确保取样处是被感染的
No guarantee we'd hit the affected spot.
要是我们用甾体醇抑制排斥反应
If we give steroids for rejection,
会使感染恶化
it'd make an infection worse.
要是我们使用抗生素治疗感染
If we give antibiotics for infection,
会使排斥反应恶化
It'd make rejection worse.
哪个恶化更糟糕呢
Which worse is worse?
要是我们治疗感染  但是判断错误
If we treat for infection and we're wrong,
她会在几小时内丧命
She'll be dead within hours.
若我们针对排斥反应用药
And if we treat for rejection
却判断失误会怎样呢
and we're wrong?
她或许能挺上一天两天
She'll probably hang on a day or two.
你的假设是她的排斥反应是超急性的
You're assuming her rejection's hyperacute.
此情况的可能性  为零
Odds are, it isn't.
得先针对最严重的恶化情况采取治疗
Gotta head off the worst worse first.
我师从苏斯医生
I studied under Dr. Seuss.
开始静注甲强龙  针对超急性排斥反应
Start with iv methylprednisolone for hyperacute rejection.
如若失败  我们再给她换上广谱抗生素
If that fails, we'll switch her to broad-spectrum antibiotics
但愿到时候还来得及
And hope we're not too late.
怎么不动
Cat got your legs?
我们刚作出的用药决定
We just decided to give meds
是基于猜测  可能会要了病人的命
That could kill the patient based on a guess.
你需要卡迪的许可
You need approval from Cuddy,
而她会要求采用保守治疗
And she'll want to take the safer course,
然后你就和纸鹤一样缩成一团不敢吱声了
And you're gonna fold like an origami crane,
所以
so...
我打算等在这里  直到得到确切的医嘱
I'll just wait here till we get our actual orders.
行  你去
Fine. You do it.
告诉她  她就是个傻瓜
Tell her she's being an idiot
总是采用保守疗法
For always choosing the safer course.
当我们的病人奄奄一息的时候
She's sitting on her ample,
她那硕大  算是匀称的
if well-formed, bureaucratic ass
官僚屁股就这样坐着
while our patient's dying.
倒要看看最后是谁像个纸虾一样缩成一团
We'll see who folds like an origami shrimp.
你要我去找卡迪要许可吗
You want me to get Cuddy's approval?
我要去更重要的地方
I gotta be somewhere important.
-坐在办公室里么  -我已经迟了
- Sitting at your desk? - I'm running late.
别管检测了
Forget the tests.
我认为年轻的那个可能有自己的想法
I think junior might have a few words to say about that.
我爱他  但他就是放不下
I love him, but he can't let go.
40美元说明他能
40 bucks says he can.
没有他的帮助  我什么也做不了
I can't do anything without him helping me
仿佛我年老体衰
Like I'm senile.
要是我回去  我绝不轻饶他
If I go back there, I'm gonna rip his throat out.
你确定你不想慢慢告诉他么
You sure you won't warm up to him over time?
跳过血检  告诉我儿子结果糟糕
Skip the blood work. Tell my son it's grim news.
我得去养老院
I need to be in a nursing home.
单独的房间
A private room.
保证有独立卫生间
Make it a suite.
这是我俩的小秘密
Be our little secret.
我的官僚屁股就这么坐着  是吗
I sit around on my bureaucratic ass?
我完整转述了你的话
I was relaying your words.
我说了匀称的  我说了匀称
I said well-formed. I said well-formed!
-你到底  -我得强硬点
- What were you - I needed to be aggressive.
你个蠢蛋
You're an idiot.
她同意福曼的分析
She was siding with Foreman's analysis.
是超急性排斥反应的可能很小
The odds are against it being hyperacute rejection.
停下  我同意你的看法
Stop. I agree with you.
那是我们开始时候的分析
That was our analysis from the start.
要是你对团队决定有意见
If you've got a problem with a team decision,
来找我
You come to me.
我很抱歉  我  我回头再处理他
I'm sorry. I-I'll deal with him later.
我说了匀称的
I said well-formed.
对于没有见过裸体卡迪的人而言
People who have not seen Cuddy naked
不改妄加评论
Should not throw stones.
她的身材真的不错
She does have great cans.
卡迪将豪斯像小狗一样管得死死的
Cuddy has House on such a short leash,
没准她还给他磨牙玩具呢
She might as well start giving him chew toys.
我们再给抗生素至少1小时的作用时间
Let's give the antibiotics at least another hour.
太惊人了  你完全无视他的恋爱生活
Amazing. And House hasn't given you one ounce of grief
他就没有找你的茬么
For your complete lack of interest in his love life?
你就不觉得豪斯就是很幸福快乐
Did it ever occur to you that House is just happy
不在乎别人怎么看么
And could give a crap about other people's lives
因为这个么
Because of it?
这样的话就太讽刺  太让人郁闷了
Well, that's ironic and depressing.
按照那个逻辑
And by that logic,
你不在乎的理由是因为你幸福
The reason you don't give a crap is because you're happy,
也就是说你有新欢了
Which means you've got someone new giving you chew toys.
你说对了四分之一
You're 1/4th right.
慢着  你是说
Wait. Are you saying...
你同时约会4个女人么
You're dating four women?
血压下降
Bp's dropping.
说明抗生素没用
Means the antibiotics aren't working.
将她置于垂头仰卧位
Put her in trendelenburg.
你们能挽救她的肺么
Can you save the lung?
信不信由你  眼下我们有更大把握
Believe it or not, we got a better chance now.
意味着是排斥反应  不是感染
This means rejection, not infection.
马上开始静注甲强龙
Start her on iv methylprednisolone right away.
哇  你讨厌吃色拉的
Wow. You hate salad.
她是真的将你死死拴住了
She's really got you tied up in knots.
我自找的  同过中间人
I caved. Through an intermediary.
我需要个方案C
I need a plan "C."
你真正需要的
What you need
是你和卡迪达成共识的方案
is a plan that you actually develop with Cuddy.
抗生素没用  甾体醇也没用
Antibiotics didn't work and then steroids didn't work.
新肺被废了  不是排斥反应也不是感染
The new lung's ruined, and it's not rejection or infection.
两种可能都是错的
The only two options were wrong.
除非不是淋巴管平滑肌瘤病
Unless it's not lam.
是淋巴管平滑肌瘤病  检测结果阳性
It is lam. The tests were positive.
那么就必是检测结果错了
Then the tests have to be wrong.
油炸锅又开始工作了
Deep-fryer's working again.
还没吃完呢
Still working on that?
没  我坐下时就在这里  我需要思考
No, it was here when I sat down. I need to think.
我想确保你们用尽所有办法
I want to make sure you're trying everything
拯救我姐姐
To save my sister.
所有办法吗
Everything?
这么说的话  就一定有个办法
Well, that must be it.
听着  我以为你们会在标着
See, I thought you guys checked the box marked,
'尝试所有其它可能'的选项上打勾呢
"Try every other thing."
我才是那个该先死的
I'm the one that's supposed to die first.
有缺陷的那个是我不是她
I'm the damaged one, not her.
她从来都不患感冒的
She never even gets a cold.
缺陷有办法在你周围的人中间散播
Damage has a way of spreading to everyone around you.
比如  你显而易见的情感缺陷
For example, your obvious emotional damage
正导致我和你进行一场辩证对话
Is now making me have a philosophical conversation
而非治疗你的姐姐
Instead of dealing with your sister.
明白那样的话会造成怎样的伤害吗
See how that might be damaging?
从来都不吗
Never?
你上次感冒是什么时候
When was the last time you had a cold?
任何轻微疼痛  肿胀  任何不适
Any minor aches, swelling, anything?
好多年了  她从不感冒
It's been years. She never gets colds.
我没问她上次提到是什么时候
I didn't ask when's the last time she mentioned it.
我问的是她的不适  哪怕是小小的不适
I asked when she had one-- even a tiny one.
没什么要紧的
It's nothing.
有时候我的耳朵有点疼
Sometimes my ears ache a little.
现在告诉我其它不要紧的
So now tell me the rest of the nothing.
我  我的胸部  疼痛  一点胸闷
M-my chest... Soreness. Some congestion.
你从未提过
You never said anything about that.
我都很少注意到
I barely noticed it
直到丹佛的滑板巡回赛
Until that skateboarding tournament in Denver.
-多久之前  -一年吧
- How long ago? - A...year?
感冒微不足道  当我想到
Cold's nothing when I think of
雨果每天所经历的
What Hugo goes through every day.
没错  我们懂  你的弟弟是个圣人
Yeah, we get it. Your brother, the saint.
而他的姐姐  则是个殉道者
His sister, the martyr.
感谢上帝你跟着我
Thank god you followed me.
现在你可以回去移植委员会
Now you can go back to the transplant committee
而我去确认
While I get confirmation.
确认什么
Confirmation of what?
是什么原因导致一年来的低水平感冒症状
What causes low-level cold symptoms for a year,
进而导致两个肺部损伤  抵抗药物治疗
Can ruin two lungs, is immune to drug therapies,
并在昵称"哩高"的城市恶化呢
And gets worse in cities nicknamed mile-high?
凝血障碍吗
A clotting disorder?
她的镰形细胞特质很棘手
She has a nasty case of sickle cell trait.
心率不齐并非突发
Her heart arrhythmia wasn't sudden at all.
搞砸了血细胞  搞砸了血管
Screwed-up blood cells screwed up the blood vessels
导致我们也搞砸了
Which gave us a screwed-up
显示淋巴管平滑肌瘤病阳性
positive for lam.
要是她能早点告诉我们症状
If she'd told us about her symptoms sooner--like ever--
她或许不会危在旦夕
She might not be dying.
不管怎样  你是对的
You were right after all.
-我从未说过镰  -要是大家都更自私
- I never said sickle - if everyone were more selfish,
世界将会更美好
The world would be a better place.
那么  她没救了
So she's gonna die.
除非我们能找到
Unless we can find
她毁了一个供体肺了
She burned through one donor lung.
移植委员会不会给她第二个的
Transplant committee's never gonna give her a second one.
那么  看来你又说对了
Well, then I guess you're right again.
除非我们不需要他们的许可
Unless we don't need their approval.
你不能建议病患家长
You can't advise your patient's parents
从他们的儿子身上提取骨髓以及半个肺
to take marrow and half a lung from their son!
那我就跟他们聊聊天气
I guess I can just chat with them about the weather.
血检结果证实是镰状细胞性状
Blood tests just confirmed sickle cell trait.
他们就会想知道唯一的治疗方法
So they might be curious about the only treatment option.
虽然最近的天气确实挺奇怪
Though we are having weird weather lately.
这是不能从活体病人身上
There is a huge reason not to
获取肺器官的重要原因
take lungs from living patients.
因为他们的弟兄姊妹会死
So their siblings can die?
他们的儿子患有先天性肌营养不良
Their son has CMD.
如果进行手术  他可能
As it is, he's gonna
不到25岁就会死于呼吸衰竭
die of respiratory failure by 25.
我们的手术将会缩短他的生命
We could cut whatever time he has left in half.
这套方案不好但至少给了他们拒绝的机会
That qualifies as a bad reason for them to reject the idea.
最糟的是连他们选择的权利都不给
It's a much worse reason for them not to get the choice.
你这是在胁迫他们做出一个选择
It's coercive to tell them!
你听过不伤害吗
You ever hear of "Do no harm"?
是大二那年讲的吧
That was second year, right?
那年我被单核细胞增多症折磨了整个秋天
'cause I had mono all that fall.
而且他们的儿子也不是我的病人
Their son's not even our patient.
我们何不从门诊部随便找个牙疼患者
Why don't we just take half a lung
从他身上拿半个肺来用呐
from some guy in the clinic with a toothache?
好主意  这样他们家人就多一个选择
That's a great idea. Now we can give the parents two options.
我们不能为救一人而危害他人生命
We don't compromise one life for another.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  说真的
Okay? Seriously.
你提建议  我遵从
You made an argument.
如果你不想让我听从你的建议
If you don't want me to defer to you,
为什么要提呢
why make it at all?
你听从我的建议
But are you deferring to me
是因为我们的恋爱关系
just because we're seeing each other?
也许
Maybe.
我想是的
Yeah. I think so.
这种关系把我搞得焦头烂额
This is screwing me up.
你怎么没事呢
Why is it not screwing you up?
我也一样
It is.
当时你要用泡沫填肺  我犹豫了
I don't know why I okayed you foaming that lung.
同意的那一刻我就意识到自己错了
I realized it was wrong as soon as I said it.
我就知道  因为你歪了一下脑袋
I knew it! I knew 'cause you tilted your head.
豪斯  我们俩都乱了方寸
House...we are screwing this up.
我得给人力资源部打电话
I'm gonna call HR,
让他们尽快找别人来监管你
find someone else to supervise you as soon as I can.
我拿到了你的
I've got your...
化验报告
test results.
你有年龄为92岁的新陈代谢功能
You have the metabolism, blood counts,
血球计数  肝脏及肾脏功能
liver and kidney function of a 92-year-old.
对于102岁的人来说  这指标很不错
Which is great, 'cause you're 102.
但不妙的是
What's not so great
人类平均寿命是78岁
is the average life expectancy is 78.
因此我的建议是你需要搬进
It is my recommendation that you move into a home
全日看护的养老之家
with round-the-clock care.
真不能相信
Oh... I can't believe it!
难道我儿子不能对我实施全日看护吗
Can't my son give me round-the-clock care?
除非他拥有两年的
Not unless you've done your two-year certification
老年看护证书
in tiburon swab technology.
那一定有别的办法
There must be some other way.
就因为他有一点轻微的刺痛感
Just because he has a little tingling
对冷热的感知有些问题嘛
and some trouble feeling hot and cold
-还有些  -你感觉不到冷热
- and some difficulty - You can't feel hot and cold?
早就感觉不到了  但我这么大年纪
Not lately. But at my age...
让我看看你的牙
Show me your teeth.
整套假牙  有点旧
Dentures. Fairly worn.
我猜带了至少十年
I'm guessing ten years old.
给我看看你的假牙牙膏
Show me your denture cream.
他为什么要带假牙牙膏
Why would he carry denture cream?
因为
Because...
他锌中毒
he has... Zinc poisoning.
但如果仅靠假牙牙膏摄取
But to get it from denture cream,
他对其用量肯定很大
he'd have to take so much of it--
这牙膏他一定随身携带
Trust me, he never leaves home without it.
老爸  你到底用了多少
How much do you use, pop?
大概一天一管  在网上买到的
About a tube a day. I buy it online.
这到底什么意思
So what does this mean?
这意外地说明了你的所有症状
Bizarrely, it explains all your symptoms.
换一副全新舒服的假牙  就没事了
Better-fitting dentures, you'll be fine.
医学上看  你没必要去任何养老之家
Medically, there's no reason to go anywhere.
医院回扣
Hospital rebate.
可能需要用在一些治疗上
You might wanna... put it towards couples therapy.
器官移植委员会
The transplant committee's...
不会再给我女儿一个肺了吧
never gonna give my daughter another lung, are they?
-是的  -还有别的方法
- No. - Are there any other options?
我们还在做进一步的观察
We're looking into it.
观察什么
Looking into what?
求你了  告诉我吧
Please. Tell me.
给我点希望
Give me some kind of hope.
这我恐怕做不到
I'm afraid I can't do that.
这事关我女儿的生死
We're talking about my daughter's life.
你为什么不能告诉我
What can't you tell me?
如果你可以救她  哪怕是一丁点机会
If there's any...chance you can save her,
什么方法都可以
anything you can try...
我们需要你儿子的一些骨髓和一半的肺
We can take marrow and half a lung from your son.
这么做会很大程度上缩短他的寿命
It would likely shorten his life significantly.
他以后可能离不开呼吸机
He'd never be able to go on a respirator if he needed to.
对大部分患有先天性肌营养不良的人
Most people with CMD need to
是必须的  他们的呼吸系统会迅速衰竭
as their respiratory function declines.
可以给我们多长时间做决定
How long... do we have to decide?
最晚到早上
Morning at the latest.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我父母呢
Where are my parents?
他们可能去处理移植委员会的那些事
They're probably dealing with committee issues or something.
他们在吵架
They were arguing.
我看见妈妈哭了
I saw my mom crying.
好像爸爸在冲她吼
Looked like my dad was yelling at her.
他们很担心你
They care about you a lot.
雨果的骨髓和我的匹配
Hugo was a marrow match?
那个已经不是现在最重要的了
We're way past that now.
他们还想要他的肺
They want a lung from him too.
是关于这个吧
Is that what this is about?
不是的  你什么都不用担心
No. It's nothing you need to worry about.
大家都在努力让你获得更好的治疗
Everybody's working on getting you the best care possible.
他们想让我们怎么做
How do they expect us to go on from here?
我们得做个选择  不管怎样都承受苦痛
We make a choice... and we live with it.
这让我怎么活啊
There's no living with it.
无论我们怎么选择
No matter what we decide.
还是冰冷虚弱  她刚才呼吸骤停了
Still cold and clammy. She had a respiratory arrest.
-我的上帝  -她怎么会在这儿
- Oh, my god! - What is she doing here?
她知道是怎么回事了
She figured out what was going on.
救回来了
She's pinking up.
她肯定是把静脉注射和氧气给拽掉
She must have yanked off her IVs and oxygen.
跑这儿寻死来了
Came here to die.
刚才的自杀行为
By unhooking herself from everything,
给她的身体带来了严重的缺氧损伤
she delivered a hypoxic insult to her body
现在她的情况急剧恶化
that started a downward spiral.
你们必须得做个决定
If you're gonna make a decision,
否则就没时间了
you're running out of time.
人力资源部找不到新监管
HR can't find you a new supervisor.
怎么会呢
How come?
豪斯  因为你无法无天
Because you're unsupervisable, House.
两个部门主任还威胁要辞职
Two department chairs threatened to quit.
那我们俩只能绑在一起了
Well, I guess we're stuck with each other.
我不懂为什么要这么决定
I have no idea why I'm making this call
或者这么决定是否明智
or if it's the right call to make.
但如果你强烈地认为
But if you feel strongly
应该把治疗方案告诉她家人的话
about presenting the parents your treatment option,
你就做吧
you can do it.
谢谢  我会的
Thank you, I will.
几个小时前
Several hours ago.
你已经告诉他们了
You told them?
我告诉了他  他来我办公室
I told him. He came to my office.
对不起
I'm sorry.
也许我应该更生气
Well...I should probably be more mad at you.
豪斯医生
Dr. House?
我们做好决定了
We've decided.
我们不同意取出儿子的肺
We're not gonna take the lung from my son.
她还在申请名单上
She's still on the waiting list.
我们会尽全力帮她找到另一个
We're gonna do whatever we can do find her another--
你们这些人到底是
What ginormous crack pipe
哪根筋不对
have you people been sucking on?
-豪斯  -你们还装做
- House! - Are you gonna pretend
让自己的女儿去死不是你们的决定吗
that you're not choosing your own daughter's death?
是我们的女儿不想要的
Our daughter doesn't want it.
也许是不想开口
Probably doesn't wanna floss her teeth either.
她只是个无知少女
She's a mindless teenybopper.
别把罪名强加在他们身上
Don't put this on them.
什么叫不能强加  这原本就是他们的责任
What do you mean don't put on? It is on them.
和他们强烈的想移植那半个肺的意愿一样
As much as they may wanna pass the lung here.
他们当然想
Of course they do.
你给他们的是一个进退维谷的选择
You're handing them an impossible choice.
是生活给了他们糟糕的选择
Life has handed them crappy choice,
但他们做出了更为糟糕的决定
they are picking the crappier option.
用一个能活不知道多久的女儿
Trading who knows how many healthy decades
去换取一个能活4  5年的残疾儿子
for four or five years in which roller-boy will be a limp rag.
不是所有的东西都能用数学公式来解决的
Not everything is a math equation.
需要我来解释一下几十年与几年的区别
Do you need me to explain the differences between decade and year?
他们的儿子也是人
Their son is a human being.
你知道他们在干嘛
You know what they are, right?
他们在衡量内在价值
Intrinsic value
我们不能替他们做决定
We don't get to decide
我们每天都这么做
We do it everyday
他们俩都需要这个肺
The two of them needed the same lung
他得留住他所拥有的
He needs to keep the one he's got.
你没必要去扮作上帝来撕裂这些
You don't get to play god by ripping out...
当我们意识到要移植时就已无路可选
That train left the station when we learn to do transplants,
剩下就只有文书工作
the rest is just paper-pushing.
因为现在的工作才是你的专长
Because now we are onto your real area of expertise
我以为我们转入了你的专长
Oh, I thought we were moving onto yours
胁迫你的病人
bullying your patients into
迎合你自己的道德缺失
embracing your own lack of a moral
雨果  亲爱的
Hugo, honey
我们不是故意让你听到这些的
We didn't mean for you to hear any of these
雨果  别这样
Hugo, please.
我想让你得到那半个肺
I want you to take half of my lung.
不行
No.
不可以
I'm not .
你能做很多了不起的事
You do so many great things.
我只是看着
I just watch.
我在那里看着  为你指导与喝彩
I get to watch and coach and cheer.
但那并不是我所做的
That's not me out there.
永远也不会是
Never will be.
如果你能拿走我的这一部分
If you take this piece of me
带在你身上
carry it with you,
那我就能真正地分享你所作的一切
then I really can share in everything you do.
这是我这一生唯一能做的了不起的事
This is the great thing I can do with my life.
我的生命中不能没有你的存在
Don't make me live without you.
我们很走运
We got lucky.
把那孩子从他们身边夺走
I did give them an impossible choice,
但我确实没有别的办法
the kid took it away from them.
刚才那场争吵
That fight
是你我回来工作后的
was the first honest interaction
第一次真实的交流
you and i had since we came back to work.
如果我们完完全全地忠实于对方
If we are painfully and brutally honest with each other,
也许我们还会很走运
maybe we'll get lucky again.
你确实有一对翘臀
You've got a big ass.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视原创翻译制作
最新最快的美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net